pinkclips.mobi 2018-12-20

# Privacy Policy - PinkClips.Mobi

**PinkClips.Mobi**

* * *

Last Modified: May 15th, 2018 

**Introduction**

The operative parties referred to in this policy are the PinkClips.Mobi website and You, the User of this site. PinkClips.Mobi is the publisher and operator of this site. Hereinafter, the website shall be referred to as "Company". When first-person pronouns are used in this Policy, (Us, We, Our, Ours, etc.) these provisions are referring to the PinkClips.Mobi website. Additionally, when the terms "the Site" or "Site" are used, these terms refer to the website(s) listed at the beginning of this Policy.  
You, the User - As the User of this Site, this Policy will refer to the User as "You" or through any applicable second-person pronouns, such as "Yours," etc. Hereinafter, the User of the Site shall be referred to in applicable second-person pronouns.  
This Privacy Policy describes how we use information received about You when You visit Our Site or when You subscribe to, or otherwise use Our online services. This Policy does not cover any information that We may receive from or about You through channels other than through the use of the Site. 

**The Data We Collect About You**

Personal data, or personal information, means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified by (“Personal Information”). It does not include data that has been anonymized or pseudonymized.

Visitors to Our Site and services will have multiple manners of interactivity with Us. Depending upon Your level of interaction, We will collect different information about You. The type of information collected is as follows: 

· Technical Data includes internet protocol (IP) address, which we pseudonymize (a technique that replaces or removes information in the dataset that identifies an individual), browser type and version, time zone setting and location, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this Website.

· Usage Data includes aggregated information about how you use our Website, products and services. 

We do not collect special categories of Personal Information about you (this includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data). However, particular preferences and sexual orientation depend on how you use our Website and services. The processing of such Sensitive Personal Information may be necessary to provide some of our service to you. 

**How is Your Personal Information Collected?**

· We use cookies to collect information about You in order to enhance Your experience on the Site. The information collected in Our cookies includes, but is not limited to, Your User IP address, geographic location and other session data. 

· Direct interactions. Information that you provide when carrying out search queries on our Website or by filling in forms on our Website, when reporting a problem with our Website, or requesting further services.

**How We Use Your Information**

We will only use your personal data when the applicable local law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal data in the following circumstances:

For purposes of providing the services, customer management and functionality and security as is necessary to perform the services provided to you under our term and conditions and any other contract that you have with us.  
Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests.  
Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.  
Where you declare your valid consent to use it.

Note that we may process your personal data for more than one lawful ground depending on the specific purpose for which we are using your data. 

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

We take measures to protect the transmission of all sensitive end-user information. We make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of Our network and systems. Nevertheless, We cannot guarantee that Our security measures will prevent third-party cyber-criminals (also known as 'hackers') from illegally obtaining this information. We take all reasonable measures to prevent such breaches of security, but given the resourcefulness of cyber-criminals, We are unable to guarantee that Our security is one hundred percent (100%) breach-proof but we assure you our best effort in maintaining one. You assume the risk of such breaches to the extent that they occur despite Our reasonable security measures. 

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

We may modify or revise our privacy policy from time to time. Although we may attempt to notify you when major changes are made to this privacy policy, you are expected to periodically review the most up-to-date version found at so you are aware of any changes, as they are binding on you.

If we change anything in our privacy policy, the date of change will be reflected in the “last modified date”. You agree that you will periodically review this privacy policy and refresh the page when doing so. You agree to note the date of the last revision to our privacy policy. If the “last modified” date is unchanged from the last time you reviewed our privacy policy, then it is unchanged. On the other hand, if the date has changed, then there have been changes, and you agree to re-review our privacy policy, and you agree to the new ones. By continuing to use the Website subsequent to us making available an amended version of our privacy policy in a way that you can easily take notice of it, you thereby consent to such amendment. 

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our information-handling practices, please contact us at 

**GDPR (General Data Protecton Regulation)**

In accordance with the General Data Protecton Regulation law in the European Union effective May 25, 2018, PinkClips.Mobi users can contact us at  regarding their data rights. 

Home
